All pirates searching for the treasure One Piece must brave the second half of the Grand Line.
These wild and dangerous seas are known as the New World.
Gold Roger and his crew were the only men to ever chart these waters and learn all the secrets they held.
For the rest of the pirates of the world, this has proven to be the end of the road, a graveyard of dreams.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body became rubber after eating the gum gum fruit, sets sail into the New World with his faithful crew.
I'm gonna be the king of the pirates!
The first stop on Luffy's journey is Fishman Island, thousands of feet below sea level, where his crew becomes involved in a civil war.
Jinbei tells them the tragic history of the island and reveals his connection to Arlong.
Despite his role in Nami's suffering, she forgives him wholeheartedly.
Soon after, the Straw Hats receive a surprise transmission.
Hello there, people of Fishman Island. Am I coming through?
Well then, for those of you who don't know, I'm the captain of the new Fishman Pirates.
My name is Horty Jones!
The Kingdom in Shock, an order to execute Neptune issued.
Come on! Next!
Next!
You won't step on it?
I'm sure Queen Otohime would forgive us.
If I refuse, they'll kill me.
I can't believe this is happening.
I'm sorry, Queen Otohime.
I don't want to.
There you go.
Next!
Kya-kya!
How boring!
No one's even trying to resist!
Ha!
People are stomping on her without a second thought!
Kya-kya!
Hey Daruma!
You gotta come see this quick!
Captain Horty's live on the air!
Huh?
So he's the one behind all this.
The bastard!
Why does he want us to stuff on the Queen so bad?
Wait!
That guy?
Wasn't he also the soldier from the plaza?
He killed Otohime's assassin that day!
That's right!
His name is Horty Jones!
The same guy!
Why would one of Neptune's soldiers do such a thing?
There's something every citizen of the Ryugu Kingdom needs to know.
This will be destroyed!
And quickly!
We'll rebuild it from scratch!
But with a new king!
Like me!
What's he talking about?
Who does he think he is?
Screw you!
This is crazy!
Where is this broadcast even coming from?
King Neptune!
Is he okay?
The Straw Hat supposedly took over the palace!
Do you think they're his allies?
Nothing makes sense anymore!
I will usher in a new era for Fishman Island!
Grounded in a strict code of discipline!
For starters, we'll end all friendly relations with humans!
So if you like them, get out!
Yes!
Fishmen are far superior to humans!
It's time that race of weaklings learned its place they don't deserve our help!
In place of the sympathizers!
Those loyal to our cause will move in from the Fishman District!
They hate humans too!
And will do whatever it takes to rid this country of them!
So treat them with respect!
Is he serious?
New residents?
He's just gonna let all these criminals roam free through our kingdom?
You still love her, don't you?
Otohime, our most cherished queen!
She was indeed selfless and worked tirelessly to build a bridge between fishmen and humans!
I do respect her spirit!
But have you forgotten the end of her tale?
She was killed by a human!
Even if you approach them with a pure heart and kind intentions,
they'll just take advantage of you and leave you in the dirt!
We have to wake up, can't you see?
Sorry, but the royal family's been duping you for years!
If we follow them, we'll face extinction!
As long as humans exist, this goal of harmony is unattainable!
It's a pipe dream that's been perpetuated for far too long!
Stop it!
See for yourself!
They have father!
How could they?
Father!
Not the king!
King Neptune got old!
It happens to everyone!
The only way to advance is to eliminate the old god,
so they won't hold us back anymore!
Huh, when you think about it, this mess is kind of our fault!
If we hadn't shown up, the king might be fine!
Huh?
More like Zoro's fault!
And that's why you shouldn't feel guilty!
Mosshead just can't keep his swords to himself, that's all!
What in the world did you do at the palace?
Jinbei, wait!
Calm down!
A bunch of Neptune soldiers attacked Namichin and our friends first!
They were just trying to defend themselves!
I'm still confused!
Citizens of Fishman Island!
The old Ryugu Kingdom has worn out its welcome!
Time to say goodbye!
In three hours, at the Conchcord Plaza, the weak and incompetent King Neptune will be put to death!
The Great Pirate Era began when the Navy executed a human, Gold Roger, the king of the pirates!
That era was notable for countless acts of persecution at the hands of humans!
It's only natural then, that Neptune's execution will bring about a great fishman era!
One in between, reign over humans!
As you may have figured out by now, I am at the Ryugu Palace, and there's something else I want to show you!
This here, is from the nobles!
The queen risked her life for this!
Ten years ago, that is!
If I destroy this letter, it's over!
You won't get another one!
Along with that, here we have a box!
With signatures from most of Fishman Island!
Frankly, I'm disgusted by the numbers!
Who in their right mind would want to befriend humans after all they've done?
So, if your name is on any of these, thank you!
I know who I have to weed out!
My kingdom will be better without you!
And with that in mind, why don't we get started?
Here's page one!
Enough stepping on pictures!
That's true!
It's far too easy to pretend you don't mind doing it just to save yourselves!
But these signatures, they give me concrete evidence of who I can suspect will oppose my rule!
It's like you signed your own death warrant!
Alright then, let's see who the traitors are!
First...
Togare of Coral Hill!
No!
Not me!
Please, I...
Second...
Gotan of Water Wheel Town!
Next is Luca from Mermaid Cove!
The Mermaid Cove!
Ah!
Five down, thousands to go!
Enjoy.
Oh, man! He even captured Zoro?!
That's what we get, leaving them alone.
But still, all three?
Do it. Right.
Do it.
Oh, no! What's this? We're going up!
This can't possibly be good.
Hello? Yes? Now what?
Something's coming!
Oh, no.
It's water!
By the time we finish the king's execution,
that room will be completely flooded.
You lowly humans can't survive that,
if I'm not mistaken.
Too bad.
Straw hand, Luffy! Look at that bounty!
Four hundred million!
The heads of you and your crewmates
will serve as a perfect warning to any humans
who dare defy us.
But for now, we're tearing down the old Ryugu kingdom!
We're done with the failures of the past.
This is the time for revolution!
Just three hours, that's all we need.
Fishman Island will take back its pride in three hours!
Yahahahaha!
We can't stay!
Still have to be alive!
Now then, issue an order to Daruma and the others to assemble.
We need to act quickly.
Sure thing, Captain.
Your execution's going to be big.
The more citizens that fear me, the better.
I don't have time to convince everyone that my way is the right one.
You're only thinking of yourself.
Even if you were right, a nation can't prosper in fear.
The truth is, all rulers are selfish.
I'm surprised.
You should know that better than anyone, Your Majesty.
Ever since I was a soldier, I've been dragged along by Queen Otohime's foolish dream.
We all have.
Thankfully, you'll be gone soon.
And then, they'll see the truth.
They'll have to.
Because my law will reign supreme.
Hey, guys.
This water isn't getting any lower.
Oh, no.
I just got dry, too.
Now, let's all figure out a way to save me.
Or better yet, save us.
Do you have any ideas?
Anything?
I'm thinking.
First, get me out of these chains.
You got it.
Psychic powers, don't fail me now.
Chains come off.
Your links are getting looser.
The metal's getting weaker.
Chains be gone.
Nothing.
Well, we're stuck.
Nice knowing you guys.
I still can't stop laughing.
Did you see the look on those fishmen's faces when I stood up?
Priceless.
He's not moving.
Is he dead?
Just keep still and they won't know.
What about this old skeleton hanging off the ledge?
How did something like that even get here?
Who knows?
Sure is weird.
Maybe it got swept up in the current when Captain Horty busted through the wall.
Let's pull it up on the bridge.
Perfect.
Brook can free us later if he keeps pretending to be dead.
Who knew being a skeleton would come in so handy?
Poor guy was probably adrift at sea.
I can't help but feel sorry for him.
It looks like he died a long time ago.
Retire!
Huh?
Ah!
I did die.
He's alive!
Somewhat.
Well, I may do at least.
The name's Brook.
Nice one, Brook.
You want to touch my Avro?
And rub him!
Why don't you rub it and make a wish?
Enough!
So much for that.
If I laugh any harder, I'll die!
We're all gonna die!
We wouldn't have gotten caught if it weren't for you!
Please help!
They're killing me!
Wait, never mind.
You're killing me too!
Well, at least Nami and the others escaped.
Soon, Luffy and the rest of the crew will come get us out of here.
Wishful thinking!
What if they don't?
As Robin would say,
Oh, I hope Nami hasn't been eaten by some deep-sea creature.
Just like her!
This poneglyph is different from the others.
Now, let's see.
It looks like a letter.
As well as an apology.
But who is this apology for?
And why did you engrave it in stone?
Joy Boy.
That's a lot of money!
$400 million?
When did that go up, huh?
No one cares about your bounty!
Obviously, they're using the others as bait.
Think about it, Luffy.
You're infamous now.
The conflict at Marine Ford made sure of that.
Once you surpass $300 million,
it rarely increases again.
Well, anyway,
if someone wants to fight me,
I'll fight him!
I beg you,
don't act rashly!
They have father.
My father needs me!
I have to help!
I'm coming, Daddy!
Megalo!
I can't just stay here!
Come back!
Shira Hoshi!
Megalo!
Don't move!
You could die!
If I don't save father,
then he...
I do understand the urgency.
But please,
you must listen!
You...
He's right.
You can't go back right now.
You too?
The one person
that Horty is most afraid of
in the Ryugu Kingdom
is you, Princess.
Your power.
Even if Horty does change the island
to suit his needs,
you'll still be a threat.
If you summon the Sea Kings,
everything will come crashing down
in an instant.
That's why he took
King Neptune hostage,
to neutralize the princess
and to lure her back.
You're saying this whole time,
they've really been after Shira Hoshi.
You.
Yes, but not in the way
you might think.
Horty doesn't want to capture
the princess to use her power.
This may sound cruel,
but he'd prefer a threat like her
not exist at all.
That's why he partnered
with Vander Decken.
Decken is capable of killing her.
Plain and simple.
He'll destroy anything
that stands in his way.
Hmm.
That's right.
Horty wants the princess
to rush into the plaza.
There,
she would be most vulnerable.
Um,
my family has mentioned
my power before,
but I'm afraid that's all.
Even if you were to ask me
to communicate with the Sea Kings,
I don't think I could do it.
Not now.
To be honest,
I'm not convinced
that I have the power
in the first place.
Whether you do or not,
Horty has no qualms
with killing you
just to be safe.
Therefore,
we must not let him find out
that you aren't able
to control the power.
The more afraid of you he is,
the better things are for us.
All right.
Are you done?
Good.
Then I'm going.
Hey, Shark,
take me back to the palace.
Ja.
I'm leaving the crybaby with you.
That cool?
Hell yeah.
Luffy,
I told you to wait.
Huh?
You don't get it.
You people have no business
fighting Horty.
What's the big deal, huh?
We can't fight
because we're humans,
is that it?
It doesn't make sense
when you two say it.
Quit complicating things.
That's right.
This battle isn't for you.
If you win,
the surviving fishmen
will go on hating humans again.
Please,
allow me to handle it.
I can't.
Not when my crew is in trouble.
It's not that I don't trust you,
but this fight is personal for me, too.
You guys.
They're both right.
Stay out of this.
Wait here.
Not a chance.
Such a stubborn fool.
Just shut up already.
I said I'm going.
Stop me if you can.
Luffy.
Since we were allies before,
I had hoped that you would honor my request.
How easily I forget who you are.
Hard-headedness truly does run in your family.
If you're not going to listen to me,
I have no choice.
Stand down, Luffy.
Or else.
Fearing that the Straw Hats' interference
may do more harm than good,
a battle of wills breaks up
between Luffy and Jinbei.
While the two friends go head-to-head,
Hordi's underlings wreak havoc in the city.
Still captured at Ryugu Palace,
the rest of the Straw Hats
launch a very peculiar escape plan.
On the next One Piece,
a rift opens up.
Luffy versus Jinbei.
I'm going to be king of the pirates!